Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series IA: General Files, A-H
  - Business Manager, Campus Operations, Office of, 1963-1968 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Business Manager, special projects, 1953-1962 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Business, School of, associates program, 1961-1968 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Business, School, documents on future of school, 1945-1963 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - C-, general, 1960-1968 (Box 70, Folder 9-12)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1961-1968 (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
  - California State Colleges, 1963-1968 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - California, University of, 1959-1968 (Box 71, Folder 5-11)
  - California, University of, faculty salary exchange, 1963-1964 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - California, University of, Santa Cruz Charter Centennial, May 10th, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Calvert House, Catholic Student Center, 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for Chicago, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Campus Development, Committee on, meetings, 1955-1967 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Campus Facilities Planning, Committee on, Administrative, 1961-1968 (Box 72, Folder 6-7)
  - Campus Facilities Planning, Committee on, Administrative, meetings, 1962-1968 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Campus landscaping, beautification, 1961-1964-1967 (Box 72A, Folder 1-2)
  - Campus Master Planning, Committee on, 1961 (Box 72A, Folder 3)
  - Campus Master Planning, University of Chicago planned development documents for submission to Chicago City Planning Department, 1961-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
  - Campus Planning, Committee on, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Campus Planning, Committee on, meetings, 1961-1968 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Campus Planning, Committee on, Subcommittee on Master Campus Planning, meetings, 1960-1961 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Campus planning, dormitories, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Campus planning, expanding programs, space, 1954-1961 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Campus planning, the North Quadrangle, The Village, Barnes plan, 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Campus planning, the North Quadrangle, The Village, Barnes plan, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - Campus planning, sketch plan, The University of Chicago, preliminary, 1962-1965 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Campus security, 1956-1968 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Campus security, Advisory Committee to the University on security matters, Elson, Ming, Sawyier, 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Campus security, personnel, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Campus security, police, dorms, 1961-1967 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Campus security, police, Medical Center, 1963-1968 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Campus security, police, (SECC Blakiston, crime rates), 1963-1965 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Campus security at the University Administration Building, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Campus security at the University Library, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Campus tours, 1963-1966 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Canadian visitors, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Cancer research, 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Cancer Research Foundation, 1960-1967 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Car-, general, 1963-1967 (Box 74, Folder 16-17)
  - Cardiovascular undergraduate training grant, Program Directors, conference, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Career Counseling and Placement, Office of, 1961-1968 (Box 75, Folder 2-4)
  - Carleton College, 1965-1967 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, 1962-1968 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, Carnegie Study on the Education of Educators, report to the Advisory Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 75, Folder 7-8)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1961-1966 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Case Institute of Technology, 1961-1966 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Case Western Reserve University, 1961-1966 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Catholic, 1962-1967 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Catholic University of Puerto Rico, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1961-1966 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Center for Balkan and Slavic Studies, 1964-1967 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Center for the Comparative Study of Political Development, proposal, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Center for Continuing Education, 1960-1968 (Box 76, Folder 3-6)
  - Center for Continuing Education, brochure, 1964-1967 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Conference Center Club, 1962-1966 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Center for Continuing Education, directorship and personnel, 1961-1966 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Kellogg, committee to plan for dedication, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Kellogg, ground-breaking ceremonies, 1961-1962 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Kellogg, planning committee, 1958-1963 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Center for Continuing Education, management and organization, 1961-1968 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Center for Continuing Education, May 9 1963 Cocktail Party exhibit of paintings, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Center for Continuing Education, room rates and food service, 1963-1968 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Center for Continuing Education, site, building, financing, 1959-1964 (Box 77, Folder 4-5)
  - Center for Continuing Education, statements of operating income and expense, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 6-7)
  - Center for Continuing Education, statements of operating income and expense, 1965-1966 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for Health Administration Studies, Administrative Council, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Center for Human Understanding, 1961-1967 (Box 78, Folder 4-7)
  - Center for Information on International Mathematics Education, proposed, 1965-1967 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Center for International Studies, 1960-1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Center for International Studies, the Administrative Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for International Studies, budget and finance, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Center for International Studies, committee to prepare proposal to Ford Foundation on comparative international studies, 1964-1965 (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
  - Center for Latin American Economic Studies, 1965-1968 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Center for Legal Research, New Nations, 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Center for Mathematical Studies in Business and Economics, 1962-1967 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Center for Middle Eastern Studies, 1965-1968 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Center for Policy Study, 1964-1968 (Box 80, Folder 1-6)
  - Center for Policy Study, background, 1962-1963 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Center for Policy Study, China studies, 1966-1968 (Box 81, Folder 2-5)
  - Center for Policy Study, fellows, 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Center for Policy Study, fellows, appointments, 1965-1967 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Center for Reading Research, establishment, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Center for Research Libraries, 1964-1968 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Center for Research Libraries, Midwest Inter-Library Center, annual reports, 1955-1968 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Center for Research Libraries, newsletters, 1964-1968 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Center for Research on Modern China, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Center in Research and Training in Adult Life and Aging, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Center for Social Organization Studies, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Center for Studies in Criminal Justice, 1964-1968 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Center for Studies in Criminal Justice, Committee of the, (advisory), 1966-1967 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Center for the Study of American Foreign Policy, 1958-1968 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Center for the Study of Developmental Variations, proposed, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Center for the Study of Liberal Education for, Adults, 1961-1968 (Box 82, Folder 11-12)
  - Center for Urban Studies, 1964-1968 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Center for Urban Studies, committee to explore creation of, 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Center for Urban Studies, directorship, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Center for Urban Studies, early discussion and establishment, 1961-1963 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Center for Urban Studies, Executive Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Center for Urban Studies, fellowships, 1963-1967 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Center for Urban Studies, lectures and seminars, 1964-1967 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Center for Urban Studies, project on physical facilities for group care of children, progress report, 1964-1965 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Central Association of College and University Business Officers, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Central Records Storage Facility, 1965-1967 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Central States College Association, 1966-1967 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Central States Universities, 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Certificates, Secretary of the Board, 1961-1968 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Ch-, general, 1964-1967 (Box 83, Folder 14-15)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1961-1964 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Chancellor, Committee on the Selection of a, 1960-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Chancellor's reports to the Trustees, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Chemical and biological weapons, use of, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry, Department of, 1962-1968 (Box 84, Folder 4-10)
  - Chemistry, Department of, faculty meetings, 1961—1964 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Chemistry, Department of, Herbert Newby McCoy, a biographical sketch and history of department, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Chemistry, Department of, space, 1961-1967 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, 1961-1962 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, 1962-1968 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, Chicago Area Research and Development Council, 1964-1967 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, Chicagoland College Career Conference, 1962-1965 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Bar Association, 1962-1965 (Box 85, Folder 5-6)
  - Chicago Board of Education, 1961-1968 (Box 85, Folder 7-10)
  - Chicago Board of Education, Commission, of School Board, nominations, 1961-1968 (Box 85, Folder 11-12)
  - Chicago Board of Education, Hauser report and Havighurst survey of Chicago Board School System, 1962-1965 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Board of Education, Hyde Park-Kenwood-Woodlawn school problems, 1964-1967 (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
  - Chicago Board of Education, new superintendent committee, 1965-1966 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Board of Education, panel on integration of the public schools, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Board of Education, sites for classrooms and new schools in university area, 1961-1965 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Child Care Society, 1962-1966 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Chicago, City of, 1958-1962 (Box 86, Folder 8-9)
  - Chicago, City of, 1963-1968 (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
  - Chicago, City of, Chicago Plan Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Circle, interdisciplinary discussion group, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Club, 1961-1968 (Box 87, Folder 9-10)
  - Chicago College of Osteopathy, 1962-1968 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Committee, Chicago Council on Foreign Relations, 1962-1967 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Chicago, Committee for Economic and Cultural Development, 1961-1967 (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
  - Chicago, Committee for Economic and Cultural Development, Graphic Arts Technical Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Committee on Urban Opportunity, 1964-1967 (Box 88, Folder 6-8)
  - Chicago Committee on Urban Opportunity, 1966-1968 (Box 89, Folder 1-5)
  - Chicago Commonwealth Club, 1962-1967 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Crime Commission, 1961-1964 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Encyclopedia of Religion and Theology, 1961-1966 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Fire Department, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, 1961-1968 (Box 90, Folder 5-6)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, Chronic Disease Hospital dedication, 1960-1961 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Home for Incurables, new hospital building plans and financing, 1960-1964 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Hospital Council, 1961-1968 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Institute for Advanced Theological Studies, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Institute for Psychoanalysis, 1964-1966 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Manual Training School, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Maroon, 1963-1968 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Maroon, study on organization, management and financing, W. W. Wick, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, Mayor Daley's Youth Foundation, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Chicago, Mayor's Committee for Economic and Cultural Chicago Medical Society, 1961-1965 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Medical Society, 1961-1965 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Chicago newspapers, 1961-1968 (Box 91, Folder 7-10)
  - Chicago, permits, 1961-1968 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Planetarium Society, 1961-1967 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Police Department, 1961-1968 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Press Club, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Real Estate Board, 1961-1964 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Review, 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Sunday Evening Club, 1962-1968 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 1963-1968 (Box 92, Folder 5-7)
  - Chicago Symphony Orchestra, campus performances, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Teachers Union, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, 1961-1968 (Box 92, Folder 10-11)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, agreements with the University of Chicago, 1963-1967 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Chicago or Chicago Today, 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Today, 1963-1968 (Box 93, Folder 1-4)
  - Chicago Today, mailings, state and federal legislators addresses, 1963-1968 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Today, volumes 1-5, 1964-1968 (Box 93, Folder 6-16)
  - Chicago Tribune, northwest Indiana, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Urban League, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Chile, University of, Industry Study Team, visit to the university, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Chilean observatory project, 1962-1966 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Child Welfare League of America, 1963-1966 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - China, People's Republic of China, Committee on One Million Against the Admission of Communist China to the United Nations, 1960-1962 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Christian Century, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1963-1968 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Christmas on campus, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Christmas cards, Mr. and Mrs. Beadle, 1961-, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 10-14)
  - Christmas cards, Mr. and Mrs. Kimpton, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Church Federation of Greater Chicago, 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, 1961-1964 (Box 94, Folder 17-19)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, Committee on, 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, directory, 1961-1964 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, meetings, 1961-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1-8)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, meetings, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, meetings, luncheon for E. H. Levi, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, meetings, dinner, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Board of Sponsors, memberships, 1961-1967 (Box 96, Folder 4-10)
  - Citizens of Greater Chicago, university participation, 1961-1963 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Citizens School Committee, general, 1962-1966 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Civil defense, 1961-1965 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Civil defense (civilian), 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, Department of, excavations in Greece, Corinth, Isthmia, 1961-1965 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland Plan, 1961-1967 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Co-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Coggeshall, Lowell T., 1959-1965 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - College, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 9-11)
  - College, 1963-1968 (Box 98, Folder 1-9)
  - College, "Artist in Residence" series, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - College, attitudes to the college study, 1960-1963 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - College Blue Book, 1958-1965 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - College building, proposed, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - College, "Celebrity in Residence" series, 1961-1964 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - College Chronicle, the, 1967-1968 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - College, College Council, 1964-1968 (Box 99, Folder 7-9)
  - College Council, meetings, 1965-1967 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - College Council, membership, 1965-1968 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - College, the College Curriculum Bulletin, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - College, collegiate division, Social Sciences, students, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - College, Committee on the College Curriculum, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - College, Committee on Multiple Colleges, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - College, Committee on Policy, elections and membership, 1961-1964 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - College, Committee on Residential Policies, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - College, committees, general, 1962-1964 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - College, conference on "The Challenge of Knowledge," 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - College, Curricular Review Committee, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - College, Development Committee for the, 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - College, Divisions, 1964-1968 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - College, Divisions, Biological Sciences Collegiate Division, 1963-1968 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - College, Divisions, Biological Sciences, Governing Committee, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - College, Divisions, collegiate divisional dinners, 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - College, Divisions, Humanities Collegiate Division, 1964-1968 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - College, Divisions, Humanities, Governing Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - College, Divisions, New Collegiate, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - College, Divisions, New Collegiate, Governing Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - College, Divisions of the, Physical Sciences Collegiate Division, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - College, Divisions of the, Physical Sciences Collegiate Division, Governing Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - College, Divisions of the, Physical Sciences Collegiate Division, mastership, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - College, Divisions, Social Sciences, Collegiate Division, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - College, Divisions, Social Sciences, Governing Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - College, E. H. Levi luncheon and discussion, meetings with faculty and students, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - College, E. H. Levi "Memorandum on the College" outsides comments, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - College, electron microscope, 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1961-1968 (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
  - College, F. Champion Ward article "Principles and Particulars in Liberal Education," 1964 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - College, Faculty Board, 1961-1967 (Box 102, Folder 4-8)
  - College Faculty Research Fund, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - College, Freshman Dinners, 1967-1968 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - College, Gates-Blake Halls conversion to Life Sciences facility and office space, 1962-1966 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - College great names well known graduates, 1960-1961 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - College, laboratories, 1963-1968 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - College, letters to spring 1964 graduating class, Mr. Levi, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - College, Liberal Arts Conference, April 4-6, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - College, "Limits of Liberal Education Program," sponsored by College and Student Orientation Board, 1961-1962 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - College, "My Life and Yours" series, 1960-1965 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - College Newsletter, 1960-1968 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - College, participation in GE College Bowl, 1968 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - College reorganization, background on E. H. Levi Memo, 1964-1966 (Box 103, Folder 5-7)
  - College, Saturday Seminars, 1965-1967 (Box 103, Folder 8-9)
  - College, self-study project, 1957-1961 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - College, space, 1961-1968 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - College, space, needs during Cobb renovation, 1964-1966 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - College students, class of 1963, attrition and graduation, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - College students, class of 1968, media, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - College, "Undergraduate Life" series, 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - College and University Business (publication), 1949-1968 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - College and University Personnel Association, 1955-1964 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - College Visiting Committee, 1961-1967 (Box 105, Folder 1-2)
  - Collegium Oto-Rhino-Laryngologicum Amicitae Sacrum, 1967 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1955-1968 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Colorado College, 1963-1966 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Colorado, University of, 1960-1966 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1962-1966 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University, 1961-1967 (Box 105, Folder 8-10)
  - Columbia University, the American Assembly, 1961-1968 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Commentary Magazine, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Human Relations, 1961-1962 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education in the Biological Sciences, minutes of meetings, Executive Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Committee of 1,000, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Committee of the Council, meetings, 1965-1968 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Committee of the Council of the University Senate, 1961-1968 (Box 106, Folder 7-8)
  - Committee of the Council of the University Senate, elections and membership, 1961-1968 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Committee of the Council of the University Senate, Subcommittee on Faculty Student Relationships, 1966-1968 (Box 107, Folder 2-3)
  - Committee of the Council of the University Senate, Subcommittee on the Ph.D. in the Professional Schools, 1961-1962 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Government Relations, Lee, 1968 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1960-1967 (Box 107, Folder 6-9)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Aeronomy Program, 1966-1967 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Committee on Instructional Resources, 1964-1967 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Council of Ten and the University of Chicago, agendas and notices, 1961-1968 (Box 108, Folder 2-5)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Far Eastern Language Instruction, 1961-1968 (Box 109, Folder 1-3)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Human Rights in Higher Education, 1963-1965 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Institutional Research Council, 1961-1966 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, International Education, 1964-1967 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Language Projects, 1961-1968 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Latin American Studies Program, 1963-1964 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Minnesota Nuclear Facility of Life Sciences Engineering, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, National Endowment for Humanities, 1964-1967 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Program in Bioclimatology, 1960-1963 (Box 110, Folder 4-5)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, Traveling Scholar Program, 1962-1968 (Box 110, Folder 6-7)
  - Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1961-1965 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Committee for the Study of Mankind, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Urban Progress, 1963-1964 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Urban Progress, 1964-1965 (Box 111, Folder 1-2)